<<<<<<< HEAD
[]
=======
[{"courseName":"Introduction to JavaScript","courseComments":[{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"Front end developers use JavaScript to add behavior to webpages.","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"},{"nestedComment":"They also use HTML to display the content and CSS to make the webpages have different colors and fonts.","comments":[],"user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"}],"comment":"Who uses JavaScript?","user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"},{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"WebStorm is one of the most frequently used integrated development environments for JavaScript, and probably the best IDE for frontend development available at the moment.","comments":[],"user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"},{"nestedComment":"I use Visual Studio Code and I really like it.","comments":[],"user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"}],"comment":"Where is the best place to code JavaScript?","user":"878a27e5-78b2-499a-847e-1c60c84cf9f2"}],"author":"51dc7b49-b0a3-4a04-a3d0-4781d1efbedf","students":[{"id":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5","grades":[65,-1]},{"id":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1","grades":[98,-1]},{"id":"878a27e5-78b2-499a-847e-1c60c84cf9f2","grades":[86,-1]},{"id":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58","grades":[50,-1]},{"id":"b7c44f2b-7b6c-4521-a361-f44941a8c418","grades":[100,98]}],"description":"JavaScript is a scripting language for creating dynamic web page content.","language":"JavaScript","modules":[{"quiz":[{"question":"How is a string formatted?","answers":["var strName = 'apple'","String 'apple'","Str strName = 'apple'"],"correctIndex":1},{"question":"You can multiply a string and a number.","answers":["True","False"],"correctIndex":1}],"moduleComments":[{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"You create two variables that are type number (no quotes) and initialize their values. Then use the variable names to multiply using the asterisk symbol.","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"},{"nestedComment":"An example is var calculation = variableName1 * variableName2.","comments":[],"user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"}],"comment":"How do you multiply two variables?","user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"},{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"An array is a data structure that contains a group of elements. Typically these elements are all of the same data type.","comments":[],"user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"},{"nestedComment":"You can access an array using the indicies.","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"}],"comment":"I don't understand arrays.","user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"}],"moduleName":"Variables","lessons":[{"content":"One way to use a variable is to hold text. You use key word 'var' to do this. Ex: var color = 'blue'.","lessonName":"Strings"},{"content":"You also use 'var' to hold numbers. You can use variables to do calculations. Ex: var size = 5. Notice how their are no quotes around the value.","lessonName":"Numbers"},{"content":"Arrays are used to store multiple values in a single variable. Ex: var colors = ['red', 'orange', 'yellow']. This example is an array of strings therefore each value is surrounded by quotes. Arrays are indexed starting at zero. For this example colors[0] is equal to 'red' and colors[2] is equal to 'yellow'.","lessonName":"Arrays"}]},{"quiz":[{"question":"What is the difference between an object and other variables?","answers":["Objects can only store numbers.","Objects can only store strings.","Objects can store a mixture of variables."],"correctIndex":3},{"question":"An example of an array of objects...var users = [{firstName: 'Ann',lastName: 'Smith'},{firstName: 'Jennifer',lastName: 'Smith'}]","answers":["True","False"],"correctIndex":1}],"moduleComments":[{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"No once you get used to them they aren't bad!","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"},{"nestedComment":"A little weird at first.","comments":[],"user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"}],"comment":"Are objects hard in JavaScript?","user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"},{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"Yes so helful.","comments":[],"user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"},{"nestedComment":"Why did I not learn this earlier!","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"}],"comment":"These are fun!!!","user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"}],"moduleName":"Objects","lessons":[{"content":"An object is a data type that can take in collections of key-value pairs. A major difference between an object and other data types such as strings and numbers in JavaScript is that an objects can store different types of data as its values.","lessonName":"What is an object?"},{"content":"You might use an object for a user. Each user could have a first name, last name, and weight. The first and last names would be a string. The weight would be a number. Ex: var user1 = {firstName:'Ann', lastName:'Smith', weight:'125'}","lessonName":"Example"},{"content":"Objects can be stored in an array. For example, to store users you could create user objects and add them to a users array.","lessonName":"Objects and Arrays"}]}],"certification":[{"certQuiz":[{"question":"What is the relationship between JavaScript and HTML?","answers":["HTML is for logic and is used with JavaScript to make a website.","JavaScript and HTML are the same language.","JavaScript is used with HTML to make webpages behavior."],"correctIndex":3},{"question":"JavaScript is how developers add style to a webpage?","answers":["True","False"],"correctIndex":2}]}]},{"courseName":"Python Basics","courseComments":[{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"Course nested comment 1 here.","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"},{"nestedComment":"Course nested comment 2 here.","comments":[],"user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"}],"comment":"Course Comment here","user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"}],"author":"3541edda-cbd8-4018-b5c9-34088171d1ae","students":[{"id":"b5622c50-86ed-4b05-a768-2aa39e8f5f5c","grades":[-1,-1,-1,-1,-1]},{"id":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1","grades":[-1,-1,-1,-1,-1,75,100,100,75]},{"id":"b7c44f2b-7b6c-4521-a361-f44941a8c418","grades":[-1,-1,-1,-1,75,100,25,75,50,50,50,100,50]}],"description":"Python is a language developed in the 90s. It is easy to understand for developers.","language":"Python","modules":[{"quiz":[{"question":"Do while loops or for loops typically use i as a variable?","answers":["While loops","For Loops"],"correctIndex":2},{"question":"When would you use a for loop?","answers":["When you do not know how long it needs to loop for","When you need an infinite loop.","When you do know how long it needs to loop for."],"correctIndex":3},{"question":"You can nest loops.","answers":["True","False"],"correctIndex":1},{"question":"What is the syntax for a while loop?","answers":["while (5) {}","while (var < 10) {}","while(int i = 0; i < 10; i++) {}"],"correctIndex":2}],"moduleComments":[{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"Loops are for good coders.","comments":[],"user":"b7c44f2b-7b6c-4521-a361-f44941a8c418"}],"comment":"These are throwing me for a loop...hehehe","user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"},{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"I don't agree","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"},{"nestedComment":"I love loops!","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"}],"comment":"Loops are fun!!!","user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"},{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"I use them a lot!","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"},{"nestedComment":"I use them for every assignment.","comments":[],"user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"}],"comment":"Loops are so helpful!!!","user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"},{"nestedComments":[{"nestedComment":"No once you get used to them they aren't bad!","comments":[],"user":"87410238-bbc8-4bd0-813b-9c04c25bc8e1"},{"nestedComment":"A little weird at first.","comments":[],"user":"41cacde1-48d5-4374-9119-4121510741f5"}],"comment":"Why haven't I learned loops before today??","user":"1f9f3f3c-fead-4c41-b2ac-98aa2fd9ad58"}],"moduleName":"Loops","lessons":[{"content":"For loops are used for sequential traversal.","lessonName":"For Loops"},{"content":"In python, a while loop is used to execute a block of statements repeatedly until a given condition is satisfied. And when the condition becomes false, the line immediately after the loop in the program is executed.","lessonName":"While Loops"}]},{"quiz":[{"question":"What is the difference between an object and other variables?","answers":["Objects can only store numbers.","Objects can only store strings.","Objects can store a mixture of variables."],"correctIndex":3},{"question":"An example of an array of objects...var users = [{firstName: 'Ann',lastName: 'Smith'},{firstName: 'Jennifer',lastName: 'Smith'}]","answers":["True","False"],"correctIndex":1}],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"If Statements","lessons":[]},{"quiz":[],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"Variables","lessons":[]},{"quiz":[],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"Objects","lessons":[]},{"quiz":[],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"Varible Math","lessons":[]},{"quiz":[],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"Classes","lessons":[]},{"quiz":[],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"Constructors","lessons":[]},{"quiz":[],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"Variable Casting","lessons":[]},{"quiz":[],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"Console Printing","lessons":[]},{"quiz":[],"moduleComments":[],"moduleName":"Writing to Files","lessons":[]}],"certification":[{"certQuiz":[]}]}]
>>>>>>> fe32255cc0ab5c983b0fa025dc64f2012bcadb57
